[

**Tasks.org**](https://tasks.org/)[Docs](https://tasks.org/docs/)[Blog](https://tasks.org/blog)[GitHub](https://github.com/tasks/tasks)

* Documentation
* Privacy Policy

On this page

Privacy Policy
==============

### TL;DR[​](#tldr "Direct link to TL;DR")

* **If you have a Tasks.org account:**
    * Your user data is stored in order to provide synchronization service. It is not used for any other purpose, and it is not shared with anyone
    * Your e-mail address is stored in order to send important service announcements. It is not used for any other purpose, and it is not shared with anyone
* **If you do not have a Tasks.org account:**
    * Your user data is not collected, stored, or shared with anyone
    * No personally identifiable information is collected, stored, or shared
* Tasks.org does not share data with any third parties
* Tasks.org collects anonymous usage statistics (see below)
* Some features are subject to third party privacy policies (see below)

If you have any questions or concerns please contact [\[email protected\]](https://tasks.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* * *

### Current location[​](#current-location "Direct link to Current location")

You can give Tasks permission to find your current location on a map. Your location is not transmitted to Tasks.org or shared with third parties

### Background location[​](#background-location "Direct link to Background location")

You can give Tasks permission to access your location in the background in order to trigger location-based reminders. Your location is not transmitted to Tasks.org or shared with third parties

Google Play only: Use of Google Play Location Services is subject to [Google's privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)

### Google Tasks[​](#google-tasks "Direct link to Google Tasks")

If you enable Google Task synchronization: Tasks will download your Google Tasks data directly to your device. Your Google Task data is not transmitted to Tasks.org or shared with third parties

Use of Google Tasks is subject to [Google's privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)

### Google Drive backups[​](#google-drive-backups "Direct link to Google Drive backups")

If you enable Google Drive backups: Tasks will upload nightly backup files to Google Drive. Tasks does not have access to any other files stored on your Google Drive. Your Google Drive data is not transmitted to Tasks.org or shared with third parties

Use of Google Drive is subject to [Google's privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)

### Mapbox search[​](#mapbox-search "Direct link to Mapbox search")

Mapbox search results are not transmitted to Tasks.org or shared with third parties

Use of Mapbox is subject to [Mapbox's privacy policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Google Places[​](#google-places "Direct link to Google Places")

Google Places search requests are proxied through Tasks.org in order to restrict usage to Tasks.org account holders. Your search results are not stored or shared with third-parties

Use of Google Places is subject to [Google's privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)

### OpenStreetMaps[​](#openstreetmaps "Direct link to OpenStreetMaps")

Use of OpenStreetMap tiles are subject to [OpenStreetMaps's privacy policy](https://wiki.osmfoundation.org/wiki/Privacy_Policy)

* * *

Google Play[​](#google-play "Direct link to Google Play")
---------------------------------------------------------

### Mapbox reverse geocoding[​](#mapbox-reverse-geocoding "Direct link to Mapbox reverse geocoding")

Mapbox reverse geocoding results are not transmitted to Tasks.org or shared with third parties

Use of Mapbox is subject to [Mapbox's privacy policy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy)

### Google Maps[​](#google-maps "Direct link to Google Maps")

Use of Google Maps is subject to [Google's privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)

### Firebase[​](#firebase "Direct link to Firebase")

Tasks uses Google Analytics for Firebase to collect anonymous usage statistics and crash reports

* Firebase anonymizes your IP address
* Firebase does not collect your 'Advertising ID'
* Firebase does not collect your 'Android ID'
* You may opt-out of usage statistics through the 'Help & feedback' menu

* * *

F-Droid[​](#f-droid "Direct link to F-Droid")
---------------------------------------------

### Nominatim reverse geocoding[​](#nominatim-reverse-geocoding "Direct link to Nominatim reverse geocoding")

Nominatim reverse geocoding requests are proxied through Tasks.org in order to comply with the [Nominatim usage policy](https://operations.osmfoundation.org/policies/nominatim/). Tasks.org does not store your reverse geocoding results or share them with third parties

Use of Nominatim reverse geocoding is subject to [OpenStreetMaps's privacy policy](https://wiki.osmfoundation.org/wiki/Privacy_Policy)

* * *

Last updated: March 2, 2021

[Previous

Tasker Plugins](https://tasks.org/docs/tasker)[Next

App passwords](https://tasks.org/docs/app_passwords)

Docs

Social

More

Copyright © 2024 Alex Baker
